koenig-solutions.com 2019-01-08

# Privacy Policy - Koenig Solutions

  * 
  * Privacy Policy 

  * Koenig collects certain information from individuals availing our services like name, contact number, email address, residential address and work information.The information is collected while going through the following procedures: 
    * When any information is requested through lead generation form, messages or calls
    * While registering for a particular course
    * When communicating with Koenig for further assistance
    * While making payment for any service
    * Connecting with us through our social media profiles/pages/groups on Facebook, LinkedIn, Google+, Instagram, Twitter, Pinterest, StumbleUpon
  * Information collected through this site is kept confidential and not passed to third party organizations for marketing or promotional purposes.
  * All credit/debit card details and personally identifiable information will NOT be stored, sold, shared, rented or leased to any third party.
  * Koenig uses cookies, tracking pixels and related technologies from third parties like Google, Facebook and affiliate marketing agencies. Cookies are small data files that are served by third party tools and stored on your device. We use cookies dropped by us or third parties for a variety of purposes including operating and personalizing the website. Also, cookies may also be used to track how you use the site to target ads to you on other websites.
  * Some of the advertisements you see on the Site are selected and delivered by third parties, such as ad networks, advertising agencies, advertisers, and audience segment providers. These third parties may collect information about you and your online activities, either on the Site or on other websites, through cookies, web beacons, and other technologies in an effort to understand your interests and deliver advertisements that are tailored to your interests. Please remember that we do not have access to, or control over the information these third parties may collect. The information practices of these third parties are not covered under this privacy policy.
  * If you supply us with your email address, you may receive occasional emails from us relating to the services we provide. If you do not wish to receive such e-mails, please inform us at [info@koenig-solutions.com](mailto:info@koenig-solutions.com) and you will not receive any future emails from us.
  * Due to overcautious spam filters, our email might not always reach you. To ensure that our enquiries are served diligently, we send a follow-up email (using an alternate email address - [koenigindia@gmail.com](mailto:koenigindia@gmail.com)) in case we do not receive a read report or a reply to our email.
  * To Opt Out mail us on [info@koenig-solutions.com](mailto:info@koenig-solutions.com)
  * The Website Policies and Terms & Conditions may be changed or updated occasionally to meet the requirements and standards. Therefore the Customers’ are encouraged to frequently visit these sections in order to be updated about the changes on the website. Modifications will be effective on the day they are posted.

### Policy for Middle East ( Koenig Solutions, Dubai)

  * In addition to the abovementioned Privacy Policy, following are applicable for our Dubai Operations:

Terms and Conditions

  * Any dispute or claim arising out of or in connection with this website shall be governed and construed in accordance with the laws of UAE.
  * United Arab of Emirates is our country of domicile.
  * Minors under the age of 18 shall are prohibited to register as a User of this website and are not allowed to transact or use the website.
  * If you make a payment for our products or services on our website, the details you are asked to submit will be provided directly to our payment provider via a secured connection.
  * The cardholder must retain a copy of transaction records and Merchant policies and rules.

Method of Payment

  * We accept payments online using Visa and MasterCard credit/debit card in USD, GBP, EUR, AED & INR currency.

Delivery/Shipment Policy

  * [Koenig Solutions Pvt. Ltd.](https://www.koenig-solutions.com/) will NOT deal or provide any services or products to any of OFAC sanctions countries in accordance with the law of UAE. 
  * Multiple shipments/delivery may result in multiple postings to the cardholder’s monthly statement

Refund Policy

  * Refunds will be done only through the Original Mode of Payment
